const cards = [
  {
    image:
      "https://images.ctfassets.net/3vnc73o2e0fb/2YxJsDD9UJPmRqUftr2xav/a82a6deaf188d316b983bb06631e441a/baby_oil-f.webp",
    question: "1000 baby oils",
    answer: "P Diddy",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question: "Who killed Tupac?",
    answer: "P Diddy",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question: "Who's got more hustle than a coffee shop on Monday morning?",
    answer: "Jay Z",
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
  {
    question: "Whoâ€™s launching rockets and probably your next car?",
    answer: "Elon Musk",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who thinks they can run for president and still drop a new album the same day?",
    answer: "Kanye West",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who designs clothes that make you feel like a cool vampire from the future?",
    answer: "Rick Owens",
    difficulty: "mid",
  },
  {
    question: "Who's so famous, even their selfies have selfies?",
    answer: "Kim Kardashian",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who's so good at data mining, they might as well be digging for gold in a reptile's den?",
    answer: "Mark Zuckerberg",
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
  {
    question: "Grah",
    answer: "Ice Spice",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question: "Alright",
    answer: "Central Cee",
    difficulty: "easy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who thought getting a shot was just another way to make headlines?",
    answer: "Donald Trump",
    difficulty: "hard",
  },
];

export default cards;
